denniskirk.com 2019-03-10

# Privacy | Dennis Kirk

####  How much information must I provide? 

The amount of information you provide depends on you. You may subscribe to our email list, set up an account, place an order, or leave feedback. 

####  What information is stored? 

We receive and store information you enter on our web site. For example, we collect information you provide when placing an order. This information would include: your name, mailing address, billing address, email address, your phone number, along with other information you submit. (eg. vehicle make, year). If you pay using a credit card, we will receive that information as well. 

####  What about Cookies? 

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on your hard drive. This enables our systems to recognize who you are. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Some information collected or stored via cookies include purchases and stored items in your shopping cart. Your browser allows you to reject cookies and software is available from third parties which will allow you to visit our web site without providing this information. You are welcomed at our web site if you use this software but we will not be able to offer you our personalized services. 

####  Does Dennis Kirk share the information it receives? 

We occasionally make our database list available to carefully selected marketing partners whose products may be of interest or benefit to you. We will not share any telephone number(s), financial information, or passwords which you have given us with any marketing partner(s). If you do not want us to share your information with these companies, you can hit “unsubscribe” at any time, or email us at [info@denniskirk.com](mailto:info@denniskirk.com). 

We may share your information with service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf (such as hosting the Website, fulfilling orders, managing databases, or processing credit card payments). 

If we sell all or part of our business, or make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, we may transfer your information as part of such transaction. 

####  What about email? 

When you purchase online from Dennis Kirk, we will contact you by email to confirm your order. If you provide us with your email address, we will from time to time email special promotions or discounts to you. If you do not wish to receive marketing or promotional emails from our web site you can hit “unsubscribe” at any time, or email us at [info@denniskirk.com](mailto:info@denniskirk.com). 

####  What about links to other web sites? 

Our web site may offer links to other sites. Other sites have their own policies regarding privacy, you may want to review the privacy policy on that site. 

####  Security 

We go to great lengths to keep your information private and safe so you can buy on-line with confidence. All credit card transactions occur in a secure area of our site, to protect you from any loss, misuse or alteration of information collected. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry standard in transferring information to process your order. The SSL encrypts, or translates, your order information into a highly indecipherable code, which is processed immediately. SSL can be identified by the key or closed lock that appears in the upper left hand corner of your browser. 

DennisKirk.com is proud to display the DigiCert Secure Site Seal. The seal is proudly displayed on our homepage to assure our customers that DennisKirk.com's site is authentic and that all transactions are secured by SSL encryption. 

We have adopted reasonable and appropriate physical, administrative and technical security practices to help protect against loss, misuse, and unauthorized access to the information you provide to us. Please note, however, that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose via the Website and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your information. 

You should never use the same password on multiple sites. If you ever think your password has been compromised, reset your password right away. 

####  Children's Policy 

Dennis Kirk is committed to protecting children's privacy on the Internet. We do not direct our services to those under the age of 13, or knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information of those under the age of 13. If we are made aware we have collected personal information from a child under 13 years old in a manner that is inconsistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we will delete this information as soon as possible. 

####  Your California privacy rights 

California law permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [info@denniskirk.com](mailto:info@denniskirk.com). 

Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to a website. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, we currently do not take action in response to these signals. 

####  International users 

Our Website is directed towards users who reside in the United States. By using the Services, you affirm that you reside in the United States, and you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, pursuant to the laws of the United States. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose information of European Union residents. 

####  Changes to our policy 

Our Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with the safest and most secure shopping experience possible. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of our Privacy Policy at any time, with or without prior notice. If policy changes are substantial, we will notify our customers via email. We suggest that you periodically review our Privacy Policy. 

####  Contact us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or our privacy practices email us [info@denniskirk.com](mailto:info@denniskirk.com) with a subject of Privacy Inquiry or contact us by regular mail at:  
Dennis Kirk, Inc.  
955 South Frandsen Ave.  
Rush City, MN 55069
